{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "How many letters 's' are in the word 'silly'?",
      "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "singleAnswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you jump higher than a house?",
      "options": [
        "Yes since houses can't jump",
        "No I have seen some weird houses",
        "No, I cannot jump",
        "Depends on the house"
      ],
      "correctOption": [0, 1, 2, 3],
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "allCorrect"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you lift Thor's hammer?",
      "options": [
        "Yes I'm worthy",
        "No, I'm not worthy",
        "Whos Thor?",
        "What's a hammer?"
      ],
      "correctOption": [0, 1, 2, 3],
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "allCorrect"
    },

    {
      "question": "Witch word in this sentence is the middle word?",
      "correctOption": "sentence",
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "inputAnswer"
    },

    {
      "question": "Do you like apples ?",
      "correctOption": ["yes", "no"],
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "inputAnswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "If Marys mom has 5 kids and their names are North, West, East, Bill then whats Marys dads name?",
      "options": ["Joe", "Is it that Thor?", "How can I know", "Tom"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "singleAnswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Witch of these are colours ?",
      "options": ["Red", "Green", "Yellow", "Table"],
      "correctOption": [0, 1, 2],
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "multipleAnswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What year is it ?",
      "correctOption": "CURRENT_YEAR",
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "inputAnswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is this questionaire silly? Pick two awnsers",
      "options": ["Yes", "No", "Cat", "Maybe"],
      "correctOption": [0, 3],
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "multipleAnswer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is this the last question?",
      "options": ["No", "Yes", "I haven't counted", "Cat 2.0"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": "100",
      "answerType": "singleAnswer"
    }
  ]
}
